<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Taking Business Forward]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Taking Business Forward]]></description>
        <link>http://projectized.co/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 22:08:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://projectized.co/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 22:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What we do?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>What we do?</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f7e8ed6b-f696-4e04-9490-7bf17e4f1e73.jpg" title="Transforming your business forward" alt="Managing projects related to your business development and transformation">,<h2><em>We help organizations in transforming their strategic objectives into actions by apply project management and PMO practices to improve business performance.</em></h2>,<p>Business dynamics have been changing in the Egyptian market over the past few years and with these changes it became clear that many firms; specially small / medium sized &amp; family businesses lack the capabilities and the necessary resources to reach their strategic goals and healthy growth objectives.</p>,<p>It was clear that there were needs for “know how” to transform, enhance, develop and implement new approach to solve business constraints with new better proven methods to look at the customer with low cost model to outsource program / project activities in most essential business strategic needs, and to comply with Projectized.co initiatives.</p>,<p>Our services are based on Project Management Office (PMO) Model. This model is usually adopted inside PROJECTIZED or STRONG MATRIX organizations types. Projectized.co saw the opportunity to implement the PMO model as it’s own internal structure and act as a virtual PMO providing project services solution to cater for our customer’s needs taking advantage of our talented PM's at PROJECTIZED.CO.</p>,<p><a href="http://projectized.co/services">Click here to read more about our services</a>.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://projectized.co/what-we-do/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b2fb2dd7-7db2-43a0-bce5-627137b206f0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence: The 3 big trends to watch in 2017 - TechRepublic]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Artificial intelligence: The 3 big trends to watch in 2017 - TechRepublic</h1><p>In 2016, the White House recognized the importance of AI at its Frontiers Conference. The concept of driverless cars became a reality, with Uber&apos;s self-driving fleet in Pittsburgh and Tesla&apos;s new models equipped with the hardware for full autonomy. Google&apos;s DeepMind platform, AlphaGo, beat the world champion of the game -10 years ahead of predictions.</p><img src="http://tr4.cbsistatic.com/hub/i/r/2013/12/14/2d2db7de-1534-4873-b3c0-8f2af1ccc213/thumbnail/770x578/ff71a61ff198a7b87fdffd7fdda24ee1/iStock_000009058764Medium.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.techrepublic.com/article/3-major-ai-trends-to-watch-in-2017/?ftag=TREe09998f&amp;bhid=23863124798107426191255506911308</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">84c0ca0f-cf33-4dc6-a995-d37c37561fbb</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 09:42:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Change]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Change</h1><p>On 13 August .1865, Dr Ignaz Semmelweis died .... a victim of learned ignorance. Official records of the time listed the cause of death as puerperal infection, a disease Semmelweis spent most of his life fighting.</p><img src="http://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/wh1.thewebconsole.com/wh/5778/images/5822b67e9c400.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.philipsmith.com.au/change.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1d331a55-3e32-4aa4-8cfa-e3eeecdf2101</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How a successful PMO should function.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How a successful PMO should function.</h1><p>The International Prototype of the Kilogram has been kept in a glass jar at the Bureau International des Poids et Mesures (International Office of Weights and Measures) in Paris since 1889. The prototype is made of an alloy that is 90% platinum and 10% iridium and is kept under strict supervision, deep within the building.</p><img src="https://media.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/AAEAAQAAAAAAAAZzAAAAJDdkNDA4ZDk5LWFiYzQtNGJlOC1hNjZmLTVkZTY1YWU3NmI1NQ.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/how-successful-pmo-should-function-greg-bailey</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f61f4272-cde6-404c-a921-f1c4d65bc261</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 11:41:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 Ways to Spend Money to Make Money]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>5 Ways to Spend Money to Make Money</h1><p>We attend a lot of fashion industry shows, like Accessories the Show and America&apos;s Mart. One of the best decisions we made was spending the extra $200 to $500 for a booth located on a high-traffic corner. There, you get twice the foot traffic you would on an aisle, and you can make your display more open to both lanes of traffic.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://cdn.ampproject.org/c/s/www.entrepreneur.com/amphtml/253030</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5c6b65f4-1c11-44fa-8c96-e46283964148</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 14:20:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[8 steps to breaking bad news to difficult project stakeholders - TechRepublic]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>8 steps to breaking bad news to difficult project stakeholders - TechRepublic</h1><p>Bad news is inevitable at some point during a project-the important thing to remember is don&apos;t try to hide it, because that will only make things worse. Be transparent, be quick about it, and be part of the solution.</p><img src="http://tr3.cbsistatic.com/hub/i/r/2015/05/07/bf3a0d33-f495-11e4-940f-14feb5cc3d2a/resize/770x/22753e7d32b4e3c851b6588c2de20a7f/300x449-unhappy-businessman-cio-box.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.techrepublic.com/article/8-steps-to-breaking-bad-news-to-difficult-project-stakeholders/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44785bd9-e215-40cc-b1e9-c65c95bd1f07</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 11:42:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time to Make Pricing, Not Just Costing, a Core Competency of the Agency]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Time to Make Pricing, Not Just Costing, a Core Competency of the Agency</h1><p>Tim Williams urges the advertising industry to catch up to the modern pricing practices of the 21st century. Client organisations have long had pricing -- not just accounting -- as a core function of their organisations.</p><img src="http://ipa.co.uk/write/images/uploads/Blog/Authors/iStock_93876371_LARGE.jpg?width=550&mode=crop&scale=both&quality=100"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://ipa.co.uk/blog/industry/time-to-make-pricing-not-just-costing,-a-core-competency-of-the-agency/12473?utm_content=buffer93ed6&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=linkedin.com&amp;utm_campaign=buffer#.V7B8QhLXenO</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">933e334d-470f-422b-a1af-387831641fd9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 15:15:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Best Thing Ever Written About Strategy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/040655c5e32e934816282d13073050346de48e59.jpg"><h1>The Best Thing Ever Written About Strategy</h1><p>This weekend, I&apos;ve been revisiting my misspent youth, by reading again the musings of Bruce Doolin Henderson and his colleagues from the Boston Consulting Group (BCG) in its early years.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/6138152</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bfb880f8-a972-4f2d-a211-a9a78aa109d6</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Steps involved in the PIP - Hands On Success]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Steps involved in the PIP - Hands On Success</h1><p>At every day assessment, there are various factors which are needed to be focused and accused if not necessary. Performance improvement is a continuous process of establishing better work plan by eradicating hurdles and obstacles which are reducing the performance efficiency. Trying obsolete approach, a gradual change can be brought for integral development of project using progressive improvement pan.</p><img src="http://www.projectmanagementinn.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/PIP.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.projectmanagementinn.com/steps-involved-in-the-pip-hands-on-success/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">710d25ad-7bf7-47f8-94b0-70a3cff9f282</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 17:26:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Production Report Template Sample]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Daily Production Report Template Sample</h1><p>Production Report is based on hundreds of different factors including planning, human resource planning, budgeting and time planning. Along with this, there are other influential factors which impart their role on the schedule of working. At most large corporations and industries where daily reporting, documentation are followed to conduct streamlined operations, excel template are devised for this purpose.</p><img src="http://www.projectmanagementinn.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/Daily-production-Report-Template.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.projectmanagementinn.com/daily-production-report-template-sample/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ba456db2-f1b1-4d2f-9c94-6a2436f3397a</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 17:26:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>