<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Taking Business Forward]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Taking Business Forward]]></description>
        <link>http://projectized.co/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 12:53:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://projectized.co/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 12:53:33 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What we do?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>What we do?</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f7e8ed6b-f696-4e04-9490-7bf17e4f1e73.jpg" title="Transforming your business forward" alt="Managing projects related to your business development and transformation">,<h2><em>We help organizations in transforming their strategic objectives into actions by apply project management and PMO practices to improve business performance.</em></h2>,<p>Business dynamics have been changing in the Egyptian market over the past few years and with these changes it became clear that many firms; specially small / medium sized &amp; family businesses lack the capabilities and the necessary resources to reach their strategic goals and healthy growth objectives.</p>,<p>It was clear that there were needs for “know how” to transform, enhance, develop and implement new approach to solve business constraints with new better proven methods to look at the customer with low cost model to outsource program / project activities in most essential business strategic needs, and to comply with Projectized.co initiatives.</p>,<p>Our services are based on Project Management Office (PMO) Model. This model is usually adopted inside PROJECTIZED or STRONG MATRIX organizations types. Projectized.co saw the opportunity to implement the PMO model as it’s own internal structure and act as a virtual PMO providing project services solution to cater for our customer’s needs taking advantage of our talented PM's at PROJECTIZED.CO.</p>,<p><a href="http://projectized.co/services">Click here to read more about our services</a>.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://projectized.co/what-we-do/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b2fb2dd7-7db2-43a0-bce5-627137b206f0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 12:45:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PMBOK 6th Edition - What You Need to Know]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>PMBOK 6th Edition - What You Need to Know</h1><p>PMBOK (Project Management Body of Knowledge) is an internationally recognized project management guide published by PMI (Project Management Institute), with the first edition released in 1996. To stay in tune with evolving practices in business, project management professionals (PMPs) continuously work to improve processes and methodologies applied in project environments.</p><img src="http://blog.epmainc.com/wp-content/themes/paula/images/body/background.jpg.pagespeed.ce.qxJd4_KZCf.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.epmainc.com/pmbok-6th-edition-what-you-need-to-know-2/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8509d553-4838-4727-bde6-0c73cd0b3419</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 22:07:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How a successful PMO should function.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How a successful PMO should function.</h1><p>The International Prototype of the Kilogram has been kept in a glass jar at the Bureau International des Poids et Mesures (International Office of Weights and Measures) in Paris since 1889. The prototype is made of an alloy that is 90% platinum and 10% iridium and is kept under strict supervision, deep within the building.</p><img src="https://media.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/AAEAAQAAAAAAAAZzAAAAJDdkNDA4ZDk5LWFiYzQtNGJlOC1hNjZmLTVkZTY1YWU3NmI1NQ.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/how-successful-pmo-should-function-greg-bailey</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f61f4272-cde6-404c-a921-f1c4d65bc261</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 11:41:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Best Thing Ever Written About Strategy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/040655c5e32e934816282d13073050346de48e59.jpg"><h1>The Best Thing Ever Written About Strategy</h1><p>This weekend, I&apos;ve been revisiting my misspent youth, by reading again the musings of Bruce Doolin Henderson and his colleagues from the Boston Consulting Group (BCG) in its early years.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/6138152</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bfb880f8-a972-4f2d-a211-a9a78aa109d6</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Financial Planning Impacts Project Management Techniques?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How Financial Planning Impacts Project Management Techniques?</h1><p>We all know that world has grown into a tight session global market where there is only survival left on the way. Things are more complex, processes have grown into multiple phases and everything requires the demonstration with practical implementation.</p><img src="http://cdn.vertex42.com/ExcelTemplates/Images/excel-templates-by-vertex42.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.projectmanagementwatch.com/2013/12/11/how-financial-planning-impacts-project-management-techniques/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">42846688-b968-4427-9d66-161ba2d604b2</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 12:53:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do You Need to Be an Industry Expert to Manage Projects Successfully?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Do You Need to Be an Industry Expert to Manage Projects Successfully?</h1><p>Published on People think they need to understand a certain industry in order to manager related projects successfully; however, technical industry knowledge will not qualify you to become a project manager, as during managing a project you are not required to know how to do it, but you will be required to know how to manage it.</p><img src="https://media.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/shrinknp_400_400/AAEAAQAAAAAAAAv3AAAAJDFlMmE0M2Q3LTNjZGMtNDIzOS04ZmM3LTNiNDVhNzk1MTkxMg.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/do-you-need-industry-expert-manage-projects-ahmed-fouad-aly-msc-mba</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3128b8ad-7059-4663-a329-3140d5c60bd7</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 11:48:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>